ifc.com 2014-12-19

# Privacy Policy – IFC

AMC PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting  ifc.com, an AMC Networks Inc. website (“the Website”).  Your patronage means a lot to us.   We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to providing you with clear information about the data we collect, how we use that information and the safeguards we have in place to protect it.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is effective as of February 13, 2013, for AMC Networks Inc. and its subsidiaries (“AMC”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). It applies to the Website and all other Websites owned or operated by AMC, including, but not limited to, AMCNetworks.com, AMCtv.com, Filmsite.org, GuySpeak.com, IFC.com, IFCAdSales.com, IFCCenter.com, IFCFilms.com, Press.amcnetworks.com, SundanceChannel.com, SundanceSelects.com, SundanceNow.com, WEtv.com and Yeahtv.com, as well as other AMC services, features, applications or functions offered or made available on or through the Website or other services or applications, mobile applications, and/or social networking applications (collectively, “the Services”).  Furthermore, the Policy applies regardless of the device used to access the Website and/or the Services (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future).

Please carefully review this Policy.  Your use of any part of the Website or Services indicates your acceptance of this Policy and your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Policy.

As we update and expand our services, we reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted here. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Website or Services after changes have been made to the Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of any revisions to this Policy.

INFORMATION COLLECTION

When you register for an account, visit certain portions of the Website, use the Services, or participate in a promotion, contest or sweepstakes, you may be prompted to provide, on a voluntary basis, certain information about yourself such as: (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) date of birth; (iv) mailing address; (v) telephone numbers; (vi) cable provider, and (vii) interests and hobbies. You are not required to provide any personally identifiable information to use our Website or Services, however, certain areas may not be accessible absent registration.

Certain third parties may join with us to offer Website activities or Services, features or promotions, such as contests or special events. By submitting personal information in conjunction with these joint activities, you are providing that information to both parties simultaneously. The co-sponsor or partner may maintain a separate privacy policy governing the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information and this Policy does not cover their collection, use, and/or disclosure.

Additionally, while visiting the Website or utilizing the Services, you may link to or view, as part of a frame on a page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party, or you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites, advertisements, features, promotions, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties.  Also, the Website or Services may link to certain third parties who offer services on our behalf. Your interaction with these third party sites and/or services is subject to the third parties’ privacy policies.  AMC is not responsible for and assumes no liability for the actions and policies of any third party business or entity.  As such, you should review the applicable third party privacy policies prior to interacting with or providing your information to these third parties.

In some circumstances, we may receive information about you from third parties (e.g., service partners and advertisers that make features available through the Website or Services, service partners through whom we provide access to the Website or Services, marketing companies that create professional marketing lists or sell other marketing data, and other websites or applications that you have registered to use, or that people you know have registered to use, when we allow those websites or applications to interact through the Website or Service to provide personalized services to you). If so, we will treat that information in accordance with this Policy.

We may also use cookies, clear GIFs and other technologies to learn about how you interact with the Website, to provide you with better service, to improve your customer experience, and for internal research and reporting purposes. We also may collect anonymous data on Website activity, such as how many people visit the site, where they are located, what pages they visit, what sites they come from, how long they stay, what items they purchase, etc. Such data is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, through the use of Internet server logs, cookies, clear GIFs and other technologies. We may also take non-anonymous data and de-identify it so that it becomes anonymous either by itself or when aggregated. We may use any anonymous or aggregated data for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and may also share such data with any third parties, such as advertisers.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.  If you decide to post content on the Website or through the Services, such as on messages boards, in comments, through social networking services, or in other postings, that information is publicly available and may be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  Such activities are outside the control of AMC and this Policy.

INFORMATION USE

By providing information on the Website or through the Services, you agree that personal information you provide may be used by AMC, its parents and affiliates for the purposes of that for which you provided it, communicating with you about your relationship or transactions with us, processing and responding to your inquiries, fulfilling your requests, offering discounts, promoting services and products, informing you about new services and products, providing news on upcoming sporting and entertainment events, providing programming schedules, conducting surveys, marketing special gift or discount offerings, offering ticket discounts, conducting contests and sweepstakes, providing information that we believe will be of interest to you, internal research and reporting, improving and developing the content and features of the Website or Services, administering and troubleshooting the Services, enforcing the legal terms that govern your use of the Website and Services, and similar purposes. AMC’s current affiliates include Cablevision Systems Corporation and its subsidiaries and The Madison Square Garden Company and its subsidiaries.

INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

From time to time, we may provide access to information to select third parties to assist us in providing services or for other legitimate business purposes. For example, we may provide access to companies providing services to us, including billing, sales and marketing, market research, fulfillment, data storage, analysis and processing, and legal services. We may also provide access to third parties who assist us in providing targeted advertising. Third parties who have such access may not use the information for any other purpose, including their own marketing.

We will disclose personally identifiable information to non-affiliated third parties (a) as set forth in this Policy; (b) where it is necessary for us to render our services or conduct a legitimate business activity related to our services; or (c) with appropriate consent. We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated third parties, including parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and joint venture partners at any time, subject to the use restrictions set forth in this Policy. You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve and disclose your account information and content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or other contracts with you; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect our rights, property or personal safety as well as those of our users and the public. We may also disclose information to law enforcement agencies in emergency circumstances, where the disclosure of such information is consistent with the types of emergency disclosures permitted or required by law.

Finally, we also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all of the information collected at our sites, including personally identifiable information, to a successor company in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all, or components, of our business.

INTERNATIONAL VISITORS

This Website is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you visit one of our sites from a location outside the United States, please be advised that any information you provide may be processed in and transferred to the United States, where privacy protections may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union or other locations. By using the Website or Services, you consent to this transfer and to the use of your personally identifiable data as described herein.

YOUR CHOICES REGARDING MARKETING AND OPTING OUT

If you have provided personally identifiable information on one of our Websites or through our Services and later decide that you would rather not have us use such data for marketing purposes in accordance with the Policy as provided herein, you can opt-out of this use at any time by: (i) going to the link provided at the bottom of any email you receive from us and opting out of receiving information from us and/or our parents, affiliates, and subsidiaries; (ii) by sending us an email at webmaster@ifc.com; or (iii) writing us at AMC Networks Inc., c/o IFC TV LLC 11 Penn Plaza, New York, NY 10001, Attn: IFC TV LLC Privacy Coordinator.

UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

To keep information that you provide via this Website accurate, current and complete, visit your Website subscription page(s) or email webmaster@ifc.com. If a member name and password were required to access the feature, you will need to provide such information to update your registration information.

LINKS

You should note that the Website has business relationships with (and may provide hyperlinks to) unaffiliated third parties (e.g. sites that offer discounts for certain products, sell tickets, sell branded merchandise, etc.) and may provide links to the websites of such third parties so that they can offer you products and services. If you visit a third party site by clicking on such hyperlink found on our webpage, any information you provide is subject to that third party site's privacy policy; and we encourage you to review that website's privacy policy before providing any personally identifiable information. The entities controlling these third party websites are responsible for ensuring compliance with all applicable laws, regulations and rules.

COOKIES

Data is gathered through the use of Internet server logs, clear GIFs and cookies. A web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A clear GIF (also known as “web beacons,”  “Internet tags,” or “pixel tags”) consists of lines of code that allow websites to summarize overall visitor usage patterns and to provide personalized services.  A cookie is a small piece of information that a website sends to a visitor's computer, which is stored on his or her hard drive. AMC uses cookies to track repeat visits to our website and to identify our customers on other websites. These cookies do not store personally identifiable information, although information in cookies may be combined with other identifiable information that we maintain. You may be able to disable some cookies by changing your browser or Flash Player settings, although some portions of the Website may not function properly if you do so.

AMC and its advertisers may use third party ad servers and ad networks, including without limitation, DoubleClick, to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and other websites and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our Privacy Policy does not cover their use of information. For more information about third-party ad servers generally and to express your preferences regarding these activities, including opting out of ad targeting, you may find more information at the website of the individual ad network, or click here to link to Network Advertising Initiatives.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY

AMC does not target this Website to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under the age of thirteen except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of thirteen in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe AMC has any information from or about anyone under the age of thirteen, please contact us at the address listed below.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Beginning January 1, 2005, California law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personally Identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to the contact information below.

CONTACTING US ABOUT THIS POLICY

Please do not hesitate to contact us with any questions, concerns, requests or comments by:

Writing to us at:

AMC Networks Inc.

c/o IFC TV LLC

11 Penn Plaza

New York, NY 10001

Attention: IFC TV LLC Privacy Coordinator

webmaster@ifc.com

SECURITY

We have implemented commercially reasonable security measures to protect the personal information that we collect. Despite our efforts, however, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable.  Please be aware that any communications to the Website or through the Services may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or the Website or Services may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative error.  Accordingly, AMC cannot and does not guarantee that the information you provide is completely secure and safe from such risks.

Copyright © 2013 ifc.com

Version:  February 2013

AMC PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting  ifc.com, an AMC Networks Inc. website (“the Website”).  Your patronage means a lot to us.   We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to providing you with clear information about the data we collect, how we use that information and the safeguards we have in place to protect it.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is effective as of February 13, 2013, for AMC Networks Inc. and its subsidiaries (“AMC”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). It applies to the Website and all other Websites owned or operated by AMC, including, but not limited to, AMCNetworks.com, AMCtv.com, Filmsite.org, GuySpeak.com, IFC.com, IFCAdSales.com, IFCCenter.com, IFCFilms.com, Press.amcnetworks.com, SundanceChannel.com, SundanceSelects.com, SundanceNow.com, WEtv.com and Yeahtv.com, as well as other AMC services, features, applications or functions offered or made available on or through the Website or other services or applications, mobile applications, and/or social networking applications (collectively, “the Services”).  Furthermore, the Policy applies regardless of the device used to access the Website and/or the Services (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future).

Please carefully review this Policy.  Your use of any part of the Website or Services indicates your acceptance of this Policy and your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Policy.

As we update and expand our services, we reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted here. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Website or Services after changes have been made to the Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of any revisions to this Policy.

INFORMATION COLLECTION

When you register for an account, visit certain portions of the Website, use the Services, or participate in a promotion, contest or sweepstakes, you may be prompted to provide, on a voluntary basis, certain information about yourself such as: (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) date of birth; (iv) mailing address; (v) telephone numbers; (vi) cable provider, and (vii) interests and hobbies. You are not required to provide any personally identifiable information to use our Website or Services, however, certain areas may not be accessible absent registration.

Certain third parties may join with us to offer Website activities or Services, features or promotions, such as contests or special events. By submitting personal information in conjunction with these joint activities, you are providing that information to both parties simultaneously. The co-sponsor or partner may maintain a separate privacy policy governing the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information and this Policy does not cover their collection, use, and/or disclosure.

Additionally, while visiting the Website or utilizing the Services, you may link to or view, as part of a frame on a page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party, or you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites, advertisements, features, promotions, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties.  Also, the Website or Services may link to certain third parties who offer services on our behalf. Your interaction with these third party sites and/or services is subject to the third parties’ privacy policies.  AMC is not responsible for and assumes no liability for the actions and policies of any third party business or entity.  As such, you should review the applicable third party privacy policies prior to interacting with or providing your information to these third parties.

In some circumstances, we may receive information about you from third parties (e.g., service partners and advertisers that make features available through the Website or Services, service partners through whom we provide access to the Website or Services, marketing companies that create professional marketing lists or sell other marketing data, and other websites or applications that you have registered to use, or that people you know have registered to use, when we allow those websites or applications to interact through the Website or Service to provide personalized services to you). If so, we will treat that information in accordance with this Policy.

We may also use cookies, clear GIFs and other technologies to learn about how you interact with the Website, to provide you with better service, to improve your customer experience, and for internal research and reporting purposes. We also may collect anonymous data on Website activity, such as how many people visit the site, where they are located, what pages they visit, what sites they come from, how long they stay, what items they purchase, etc. Such data is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, through the use of Internet server logs, cookies, clear GIFs and other technologies. We may also take non-anonymous data and de-identify it so that it becomes anonymous either by itself or when aggregated. We may use any anonymous or aggregated data for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and may also share such data with any third parties, such as advertisers.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.  If you decide to post content on the Website or through the Services, such as on messages boards, in comments, through social networking services, or in other postings, that information is publicly available and may be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  Such activities are outside the control of AMC and this Policy.

INFORMATION USE

By providing information on the Website or through the Services, you agree that personal information you provide may be used by AMC, its parents and affiliates for the purposes of that for which you provided it, communicating with you about your relationship or transactions with us, processing and responding to your inquiries, fulfilling your requests, offering discounts, promoting services and products, informing you about new services and products, providing news on upcoming sporting and entertainment events, providing programming schedules, conducting surveys, marketing special gift or discount offerings, offering ticket discounts, conducting contests and sweepstakes, providing information that we believe will be of interest to you, internal research and reporting, improving and developing the content and features of the Website or Services, administering and troubleshooting the Services, enforcing the legal terms that govern your use of the Website and Services, and similar purposes. AMC’s current affiliates include Cablevision Systems Corporation and its subsidiaries and The Madison Square Garden Company and its subsidiaries.

INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

From time to time, we may provide access to information to select third parties to assist us in providing services or for other legitimate business purposes. For example, we may provide access to companies providing services to us, including billing, sales and marketing, market research, fulfillment, data storage, analysis and processing, and legal services. We may also provide access to third parties who assist us in providing targeted advertising. Third parties who have such access may not use the information for any other purpose, including their own marketing.

We will disclose personally identifiable information to non-affiliated third parties (a) as set forth in this Policy; (b) where it is necessary for us to render our services or conduct a legitimate business activity related to our services; or (c) with appropriate consent. We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated third parties, including parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and joint venture partners at any time, subject to the use restrictions set forth in this Policy. You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve and disclose your account information and content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or other contracts with you; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect our rights, property or personal safety as well as those of our users and the public. We may also disclose information to law enforcement agencies in emergency circumstances, where the disclosure of such information is consistent with the types of emergency disclosures permitted or required by law.

Finally, we also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all of the information collected at our sites, including personally identifiable information, to a successor company in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all, or components, of our business.

INTERNATIONAL VISITORS

This Website is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you visit one of our sites from a location outside the United States, please be advised that any information you provide may be processed in and transferred to the United States, where privacy protections may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union or other locations. By using the Website or Services, you consent to this transfer and to the use of your personally identifiable data as described herein.

YOUR CHOICES REGARDING MARKETING AND OPTING OUT

If you have provided personally identifiable information on one of our Websites or through our Services and later decide that you would rather not have us use such data for marketing purposes in accordance with the Policy as provided herein, you can opt-out of this use at any time by: (i) going to the link provided at the bottom of any email you receive from us and opting out of receiving information from us and/or our parents, affiliates, and subsidiaries; (ii) by sending us an email at webmaster@ifc.com; or (iii) writing us at AMC Networks Inc., c/o IFC TV LLC 11 Penn Plaza, New York, NY 10001, Attn: IFC TV LLC Privacy Coordinator.

UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

To keep information that you provide via this Website accurate, current and complete, visit your Website subscription page(s) or email webmaster@ifc.com. If a member name and password were required to access the feature, you will need to provide such information to update your registration information.

LINKS

You should note that the Website has business relationships with (and may provide hyperlinks to) unaffiliated third parties (e.g. sites that offer discounts for certain products, sell tickets, sell branded merchandise, etc.) and may provide links to the websites of such third parties so that they can offer you products and services. If you visit a third party site by clicking on such hyperlink found on our webpage, any information you provide is subject to that third party site's privacy policy; and we encourage you to review that website's privacy policy before providing any personally identifiable information. The entities controlling these third party websites are responsible for ensuring compliance with all applicable laws, regulations and rules.

COOKIES

Data is gathered through the use of Internet server logs, clear GIFs and cookies. A web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A clear GIF (also known as “web beacons,”  “Internet tags,” or “pixel tags”) consists of lines of code that allow websites to summarize overall visitor usage patterns and to provide personalized services.  A cookie is a small piece of information that a website sends to a visitor's computer, which is stored on his or her hard drive. AMC uses cookies to track repeat visits to our website and to identify our customers on other websites. These cookies do not store personally identifiable information, although information in cookies may be combined with other identifiable information that we maintain. You may be able to disable some cookies by changing your browser or Flash Player settings, although some portions of the Website may not function properly if you do so.

AMC and its advertisers may use third party ad servers and ad networks, including without limitation, DoubleClick, to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and other websites and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our Privacy Policy does not cover their use of information. For more information about third-party ad servers generally and to express your preferences regarding these activities, including opting out of ad targeting, you may find more information at the website of the individual ad network, or click here to link to Network Advertising Initiatives.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY

AMC does not target this Website to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under the age of thirteen except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of thirteen in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe AMC has any information from or about anyone under the age of thirteen, please contact us at the address listed below.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Beginning January 1, 2005, California law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personally Identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to the contact information below.

CONTACTING US ABOUT THIS POLICY

Please do not hesitate to contact us with any questions, concerns, requests or comments by:

Writing to us at:

AMC Networks Inc.

c/o IFC TV LLC

11 Penn Plaza

New York, NY 10001

Attention: IFC TV LLC Privacy Coordinator

webmaster@ifc.com

SECURITY

We have implemented commercially reasonable security measures to protect the personal information that we collect. Despite our efforts, however, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable.  Please be aware that any communications to the Website or through the Services may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or the Website or Services may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative error.  Accordingly, AMC cannot and does not guarantee that the information you provide is completely secure and safe from such risks.

Copyright © 2013 ifc.com

Version:  February 2013

AMC PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting  ifc.com, an AMC Networks Inc. website (“the Website”).  Your patronage means a lot to us.   We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to providing you with clear information about the data we collect, how we use that information and the safeguards we have in place to protect it.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is effective as of February 13, 2013, for AMC Networks Inc. and its subsidiaries (“AMC”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). It applies to the Website and all other Websites owned or operated by AMC, including, but not limited to, AMCNetworks.com, AMCtv.com, Filmsite.org, GuySpeak.com, IFC.com, IFCAdSales.com, IFCCenter.com, IFCFilms.com, Press.amcnetworks.com, SundanceChannel.com, SundanceSelects.com, SundanceNow.com, WEtv.com and Yeahtv.com, as well as other AMC services, features, applications or functions offered or made available on or through the Website or other services or applications, mobile applications, and/or social networking applications (collectively, “the Services”).  Furthermore, the Policy applies regardless of the device used to access the Website and/or the Services (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future).

Please carefully review this Policy.  Your use of any part of the Website or Services indicates your acceptance of this Policy and your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Policy.

As we update and expand our services, we reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted here. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Website or Services after changes have been made to the Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of any revisions to this Policy.

INFORMATION COLLECTION

When you register for an account, visit certain portions of the Website, use the Services, or participate in a promotion, contest or sweepstakes, you may be prompted to provide, on a voluntary basis, certain information about yourself such as: (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) date of birth; (iv) mailing address; (v) telephone numbers; (vi) cable provider, and (vii) interests and hobbies. You are not required to provide any personally identifiable information to use our Website or Services, however, certain areas may not be accessible absent registration.

Certain third parties may join with us to offer Website activities or Services, features or promotions, such as contests or special events. By submitting personal information in conjunction with these joint activities, you are providing that information to both parties simultaneously. The co-sponsor or partner may maintain a separate privacy policy governing the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information and this Policy does not cover their collection, use, and/or disclosure.

Additionally, while visiting the Website or utilizing the Services, you may link to or view, as part of a frame on a page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party, or you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites, advertisements, features, promotions, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties.  Also, the Website or Services may link to certain third parties who offer services on our behalf. Your interaction with these third party sites and/or services is subject to the third parties’ privacy policies.  AMC is not responsible for and assumes no liability for the actions and policies of any third party business or entity.  As such, you should review the applicable third party privacy policies prior to interacting with or providing your information to these third parties.

In some circumstances, we may receive information about you from third parties (e.g., service partners and advertisers that make features available through the Website or Services, service partners through whom we provide access to the Website or Services, marketing companies that create professional marketing lists or sell other marketing data, and other websites or applications that you have registered to use, or that people you know have registered to use, when we allow those websites or applications to interact through the Website or Service to provide personalized services to you). If so, we will treat that information in accordance with this Policy.

We may also use cookies, clear GIFs and other technologies to learn about how you interact with the Website, to provide you with better service, to improve your customer experience, and for internal research and reporting purposes. We also may collect anonymous data on Website activity, such as how many people visit the site, where they are located, what pages they visit, what sites they come from, how long they stay, what items they purchase, etc. Such data is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, through the use of Internet server logs, cookies, clear GIFs and other technologies. We may also take non-anonymous data and de-identify it so that it becomes anonymous either by itself or when aggregated. We may use any anonymous or aggregated data for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and may also share such data with any third parties, such as advertisers.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.  If you decide to post content on the Website or through the Services, such as on messages boards, in comments, through social networking services, or in other postings, that information is publicly available and may be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  Such activities are outside the control of AMC and this Policy.

INFORMATION USE

By providing information on the Website or through the Services, you agree that personal information you provide may be used by AMC, its parents and affiliates for the purposes of that for which you provided it, communicating with you about your relationship or transactions with us, processing and responding to your inquiries, fulfilling your requests, offering discounts, promoting services and products, informing you about new services and products, providing news on upcoming sporting and entertainment events, providing programming schedules, conducting surveys, marketing special gift or discount offerings, offering ticket discounts, conducting contests and sweepstakes, providing information that we believe will be of interest to you, internal research and reporting, improving and developing the content and features of the Website or Services, administering and troubleshooting the Services, enforcing the legal terms that govern your use of the Website and Services, and similar purposes. AMC’s current affiliates include Cablevision Systems Corporation and its subsidiaries and The Madison Square Garden Company and its subsidiaries.

INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

From time to time, we may provide access to information to select third parties to assist us in providing services or for other legitimate business purposes. For example, we may provide access to companies providing services to us, including billing, sales and marketing, market research, fulfillment, data storage, analysis and processing, and legal services. We may also provide access to third parties who assist us in providing targeted advertising. Third parties who have such access may not use the information for any other purpose, including their own marketing.

We will disclose personally identifiable information to non-affiliated third parties (a) as set forth in this Policy; (b) where it is necessary for us to render our services or conduct a legitimate business activity related to our services; or (c) with appropriate consent. We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated third parties, including parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and joint venture partners at any time, subject to the use restrictions set forth in this Policy. You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve and disclose your account information and content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or other contracts with you; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect our rights, property or personal safety as well as those of our users and the public. We may also disclose information to law enforcement agencies in emergency circumstances, where the disclosure of such information is consistent with the types of emergency disclosures permitted or required by law.

Finally, we also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all of the information collected at our sites, including personally identifiable information, to a successor company in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all, or components, of our business.

INTERNATIONAL VISITORS

This Website is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you visit one of our sites from a location outside the United States, please be advised that any information you provide may be processed in and transferred to the United States, where privacy protections may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union or other locations. By using the Website or Services, you consent to this transfer and to the use of your personally identifiable data as described herein.

YOUR CHOICES REGARDING MARKETING AND OPTING OUT

If you have provided personally identifiable information on one of our Websites or through our Services and later decide that you would rather not have us use such data for marketing purposes in accordance with the Policy as provided herein, you can opt-out of this use at any time by: (i) going to the link provided at the bottom of any email you receive from us and opting out of receiving information from us and/or our parents, affiliates, and subsidiaries; (ii) by sending us an email at webmaster@ifc.com; or (iii) writing us at AMC Networks Inc., c/o IFC TV LLC 11 Penn Plaza, New York, NY 10001, Attn: IFC TV LLC Privacy Coordinator.

UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

To keep information that you provide via this Website accurate, current and complete, visit your Website subscription page(s) or email webmaster@ifc.com. If a member name and password were required to access the feature, you will need to provide such information to update your registration information.

LINKS

You should note that the Website has business relationships with (and may provide hyperlinks to) unaffiliated third parties (e.g. sites that offer discounts for certain products, sell tickets, sell branded merchandise, etc.) and may provide links to the websites of such third parties so that they can offer you products and services. If you visit a third party site by clicking on such hyperlink found on our webpage, any information you provide is subject to that third party site's privacy policy; and we encourage you to review that website's privacy policy before providing any personally identifiable information. The entities controlling these third party websites are responsible for ensuring compliance with all applicable laws, regulations and rules.

COOKIES

Data is gathered through the use of Internet server logs, clear GIFs and cookies. A web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A clear GIF (also known as “web beacons,”  “Internet tags,” or “pixel tags”) consists of lines of code that allow websites to summarize overall visitor usage patterns and to provide personalized services.  A cookie is a small piece of information that a website sends to a visitor's computer, which is stored on his or her hard drive. AMC uses cookies to track repeat visits to our website and to identify our customers on other websites. These cookies do not store personally identifiable information, although information in cookies may be combined with other identifiable information that we maintain. You may be able to disable some cookies by changing your browser or Flash Player settings, although some portions of the Website may not function properly if you do so.

AMC and its advertisers may use third party ad servers and ad networks, including without limitation, DoubleClick, to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and other websites and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our Privacy Policy does not cover their use of information. For more information about third-party ad servers generally and to express your preferences regarding these activities, including opting out of ad targeting, you may find more information at the website of the individual ad network, or click here to link to Network Advertising Initiatives.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY

AMC does not target this Website to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under the age of thirteen except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of thirteen in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe AMC has any information from or about anyone under the age of thirteen, please contact us at the address listed below.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Beginning January 1, 2005, California law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personally Identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to the contact information below.

CONTACTING US ABOUT THIS POLICY

Please do not hesitate to contact us with any questions, concerns, requests or comments by:

Writing to us at:

AMC Networks Inc.

c/o IFC TV LLC

11 Penn Plaza

New York, NY 10001

Attention: IFC TV LLC Privacy Coordinator

webmaster@ifc.com

SECURITY

We have implemented commercially reasonable security measures to protect the personal information that we collect. Despite our efforts, however, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable.  Please be aware that any communications to the Website or through the Services may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or the Website or Services may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative error.  Accordingly, AMC cannot and does not guarantee that the information you provide is completely secure and safe from such risks.

Copyright © 2013 ifc.com

Version:  February 2013

Copyright © 2014 IFC TV LLC. All rights reserved.
